Good thing Scruffy rescued Leela.
斯格拉菲救了莉拉   真是太好了
Don't thank me, thank the ladder.
别谢我   感谢梯子
Your cloned arms should be fully grown in a month or so.
你的克隆手臂将在一个月左右培育出来
But for right now, enjoy the sounds of the world's smallest violin.
但现在   好好享受世界上最小的小提琴表演
I hope you're not too mad at me, Leela. For tearing your arm off and all.
莉拉   我弄断了你的胳膊   希望你不要太生我的气
I can't be mad. I'm on way too many painkillers.
我不会生气的   我用了太多的止痛药了
Plus, you were willing to sacrifice yourself so I could live!
另外   你愿意牺牲你自己   我才能活下来
I mean, you failed... miserably...
你虽然惨败了
but you're the only person who loves me enough to try.
但你是唯一一个爱我爱到愿意为我去牺牲自己的人
One last...foolish gesture?
最后一次拥抱